<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DataBinding</string>

    <string name="likes">Likes</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="profile_name">NAME</string>
    <string name="profile_lastname">LAST NAME</string>
    <string name="last_name_label">Last name</string>
    <string name="name_label">Name</string>
    <string name="profile_avatar_cd">Profile\'s avatar</string>
    <string name="like">Like</string>

    <!-- Placeholder text for this example. -->
    <string name="title1">Googles Android is Eating Apples Lunch</string>
    <string name="article1">Smartphones and tablets powered by Googles Android software are devouring the mobile gadget market, eating into Apples turf by feeding appetites for innovation and low prices, analysts say. "Android has been one of the primary growth engines of the smartphone market since it was launched in 2008," said IDCs mobile phones research manager Ramon Llamas.

"In every year since then, Android has effectively outpaced the market and taken market share from the competition."
    "Having a lot of people building a lot of things covering a lot of price points with multiple brands in multiple places makes a big difference," said NPD Group analyst Stephen Baker.

"Variety is strength when it comes to moving units."

Android smartphones shipments surged to 136 million, topping those in the same three-month period last year by slightly more than 90%, IDC reported

    </string>
    <string name="title2">My Bonnie - Ain’t She Sweet</string>
    <string name="article2">At the same session, the Beatles played on “My Bonnie” (the first-ever single with Beatles playing), as the backing band for English singer Tony Sheridan, originally a member of the Jets. The popularity of this single in Liverpool brought the Beatles to the attention of Brian Epstein, who worked in the NEMS record store and tried to meet demand for the disc. John Lennon then sings a fine “Ain’t She Sweet” (his first-ever released vocal).</string>

    <!-- Text for the fragment. -->
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes_message">ARTICLE: Like</string>
    <string name="no_message">ARTICLE: Thanks</string>
    <string name="question_article">LIKE THE ARTICLE?</string>

    <!-- Text for the button in FragmentExample2. -->
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- Text for the exception message in FragmentCommunicate. -->
    <string name="exception_message">must implement OnFragmentInteractionListener</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="my_rating">My Rating:</string>
    <string name="question_the_song">LIKE THE SONG?</string>

</resources>